Welcome to the wonderful world of Connie.
In this short lesson, I'll show you how easy it is to get help from the Connie Care Team using the built-in Support Ticketing system.
You can access the ticketing system by clicking the Get Support button you see in the information panel.
Once you arrive at the Support Center, you have a few options.
In this lesson we're focused on opening a new ticket, so simply click Create New Ticket.
To save you time, Connie fills in your name and email automatically.
Just confirm they're correct.
Then add a brief description of what's going on, along with any helpful details, and click Send.
That's it!
You'll see an on-screen confirmation with your ticket number, and you'll receive an email confirmation shortly.
If you don't see it, be sure to check your spam folder.
The Connie Care Team will respond as quickly as possible.
You can monitor your ticket's progress any time by returning to the Get Support page.
From here, click See all tickets to view everything for your account.
Just switch the filter to All to see them all.
Or look up a single ticket instantly by typing its number into the Track box.
Just like that, you have direct access to the Connie Care Team, right from your Connie account.
Thanks for using Connie.
We can't wait to see all the amazing things you do with it.